Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Administration Records 1853-2002 (bulk, 1929-1995) MS 3009-RG 5
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.B. President, Chairman of the Board, and Chairman of the Executive Committee: James A. Linen Files, 1941-1977; 10.43 Linear feet in 11 record cartons
  - Subseries II.B.2. Speech Files, 1941-1977; 4.13 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    - By City: Asheville, North Carolina: Southeast Regional Conference: 1957 April 25 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 12)
    - By City: Atlanta, Georgia: Atlanta Rotary Club Lunch: 1958 May 26 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 13)
    - By City: Atlanta, Georgia: Southeastern Area Red Cross National Fund Vice Chairman: 1963 September 10-11 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 14)
    - By City: Baltimore, Maryland: Community Chest Annual Meeting: 1958 May 19 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 15)
    - By City: Bangkok, Thailand: Council of World Affairs and International Laws: 1966 February 1 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 16)
    - By City: Barberton, Ohio: Barberton-Norton United Fund: 1958 September 26 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 17)
    - By City: Beaumont, Texas: Civic Clubs Lunch, Beaumont United Appeals: 1957 October 19 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 18)
    - By City: Bedford, New York: United Fund of Northern Westchester County, Inc.: 1958 November 19 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 19)
    - By City: Birmingham, Alabama: National Urban League Annual Meeting: 1969 May 20 (Linen was sick; delivered by D. McGannon) (Offsite-box 597, Folder 20)
    - By City: Boston, Massachusetts: United Fund Luncheon: 1957 November 20 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 21)
    - By City: Boston, Massachusetts: Harvard Business School Association: National Business Conference: 1961 June 9 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 22)
    - By City: Boston, Massachusetts: United Fund of Greater Boston: 1962 September 25 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 23)
    - By City: Boston, Massachusetts: Magazine Seminar at Harvard Graduate School of Business Administration: 1963 May 27 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 24)
    - By City: Boston, Massachusetts: Stockholders Meeting Federal Reserve Bank of Boston: 1968 October 10 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 25)
    - By City: Boston, Massachusetts: Boston Museum of Science: 1969 October 14 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 26)
    - By City: Bridgeport, Connecticut: Bridgeport Engineering Institute Commencement: 1959 June 16 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 27)
    - By City: Camden, New Jersey: Camden County Council of Community Services Annual Meeting: 1958 March 17 (Offsite-box 597, Folder 28)
    - By City: Charlotte, North Carolina: United Community Services: 1956 March 15 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 1)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: Executives Club: 1956 September 28 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 2)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: Midwest Regional Conference: 1957 February 20-22 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 3)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: Welfare Council of Metropolitan Chicago: 1957 February 21 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 4)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: The American Bankers Association: 1959 January 22 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 5)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: AFL-CIO National Conference on Community Services: 1959 June 4 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 6)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: Supervisory and Management Group: 1962 September 27 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 7)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: Chicago Red Cross County Communities Campaign: 1964 February 17 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 8)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: Chicago Council of Graphic Arts: 1967 January 16 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 9)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: Investment Anaalysts Society of Chicago: 1968 May 23 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 10)
    - By City: Chicago, Illinois: 6th Annual Protestant Business Leaders Dinner: 1968 December 10 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 11)
    - By City: Cincinnati, Ohio: Community Chests and Councils: 1955 January 13-14 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 12)
    - By City: Cleveland, Ohio: Community Chest and Council: 1954 October 18 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 13)
    - By City: Cleveland, Ohio: Community Chest and Council: 1955 March 1 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 14)
    - By City: Cleveland, Ohio: United Community Funds and Councils of American Biennial Conference: 1958 February 26-27 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 15)
    - By City: Denver, Colorado: Combined Community Chest-United Funds Kickoff Dinner: 1956 October 22 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 16)
    - By City: Detroit, Michigan: United Community Funds and Councils Biennial: 1956 February 9-10 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 17)
    - By City: Detroit, Michigan: American Red Cross Detroit Chapter Annual Meeting: 1961 September 22 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 18)
    - By City: Detroit, Michigan: United Community Services 50th Anniversary: 1967 September 28 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 19)
    - By City: Detroit, Michigan: National Urban League: 1971 July (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 20)
    - By City: Dixville Notch, New Hampshire: Connecticut General Life Insurance Company (Presidents Club): 1958 June 25 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 21)
    - By City: East Meadow, New York: Nassau County Chapter American Red Cross: 1959 September 30 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 22)
    - By City: East Orange, New Jersey: United Community Services of the Oranges and Maplewood: 1957 February 18 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 23)
    - By City: Easton, Pennsylvania: United Fund of Easton Area Kickoff Dinner: 1959 October 7 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 24)
    - By City: French Lick, Indiana: Indiana Bankers Association 64th Annual Convention: 1961 June 7 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 25)
    - By City: Garden City, New York: Ad Hoc Committee for Nassau, Suffolk United Fund: 1963 November 21 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 26)
    - By City: Grand Rapids, Michigan: United Fund Kickoff Luncheon: 1968 October 1 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 27)
    - By City: Greenwich, Connecticut: Community Chest and Council: 1956 February 28 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 28)
    - By City: Greenwich, Connecticut: Greenwich Hospital School of Nursing Graduation: 1960 June 10 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 29)
    - By City: Greenwich, Connecticut: Greenwich Red Cross Annual Meeting: 1964 April 18 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 30)
    - By City: Greenwich, Connecticut: Greenwich Community Planning Forum: 1967 March 6 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 31)
    - By City: Greenwich, Connecticut: Urgan League: 1975 June 26 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 32)
    - By City: Hartford, Connecticut: Red Cross Annual Meeting: 1963 November 14 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 33)
    - By City: Hartford, Connecticut: Urban League Annual Dinner: 1969 April 3 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 34)
    - By City: Hot Springs, Virginia: Business Council Panel on Inflationary Trends: 1969 May 9 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 35)
    - By City: Houston, Texas: National Alcoholic Beverage Control Association: 1958 September 9 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 36)
    - By City: Houston, Texas: The Houston Society of Financial Analysts: 1967 January 18 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 37)
    - By City: Indianapolis, Indiana: Junior Chamber of Commerce Sales Executive Council Ad Club: 1961 December 7 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 38)
    - By City: Jacksonville, ___: National Urban League: 1972 February 17 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 39)
    - By City: Kansas City, Missouri: Japan-U.S. Businessmen: 1975 June 19, 1972 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 40)
    - By City: Lakeville, Connecticut: Hotchkiss School: 1968 June 6 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 41)
    - By City: Lancaster, Pennsylvania: Lancaster County Manufacturers Association: 1958 January 31 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 42)
    - By City: Los Angeles, California: Community Chests and Councils: 1954 November 4 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 43)
    - By City: Los Angeles, California: Red Cross Kickoff Lunch: 1963 February 28 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 44)
    - By City: Los Angeles, California: Associated Business Publications Program at Los Angeles Rotary Club: 1963 May 24 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 45)
    - By City: Los Angeles, California: Society of Security Analysts: 1965 October 19 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 46)
    - By City: Los Angeles, California: National Urban League dinner: 1970 November 24 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 47)
    - By City: Louisville, Kentucky: Health and Welfare Council Annual Meeting: 1960 June 3 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 48)
    - By City: Community Chest Lunch: 1957 September 24 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 49)
    - By City: Milwaukee, Wisconsin: Milwaukee-Waukesha Chapter of American Red Cross: 1963 June 3 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 50)
    - By City: Minneapolis, Minnesota: Community Chest: 1955 October 3 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 51)
    - By City: Minneapolis, Minnesota: Five Fifty-Five Club: 1963 April 8 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 52)
    - By City: Montreal, Quebec, Canada: Montreal Special Luncheon: Social workers and business community: 1961 February 1 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 53)
    - By City: Montreal, Quebec, Canada: International Chamber of Commerce XXI Congress: 1967 May 16 (Offsite-box 4195, Folder 54)
    - By City: New Haven, Connecticut: Yale ROTC: 1960 April 18 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 1)
    - By City: New Haven, Connecticut: Connecticut Bar Association: 1967 October 17 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 2)
    - By City: New Orleans, Louisiana: Community Chests: 1952 November 18 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 3)
    - By City: New Orleans, Louisiana: United Fund Special Prospects Kickoff Breakfast: 1957 September 17 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 4)
    - By City: New Orleans, Louisiana: National Alcoholic Beverage Control Association: 1964 November 16 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 5)
    - By City: New Orleans, Louisiana: National Urban League Conference Presidential Dinner: 1968 July 31 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 6)
    - By City: New York, New York: Hotchkiss Alumni Dinner: 1957 May 1 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 7)
    - By City: New York, New York: Association of National Advertisers, International Workshop: 1958 September 25 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 8)
    - By City: New York, New York: Public Relations Society: 1961 April 6 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 9)
    - By City: New York, New York: McKay-Shields Economics, Inc. Dinner Forum Panel: 1962 December 3 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 10)
    - By City: New York, New York: Seraphic Secretaries of America Bosses Dinner: 1964 May 4 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 11)
    - By City: New York, New York: Luce Dinner: 1964 May 25 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 12)
    - By City: New York, New York: Bankers Trust Company Lunch: 1964 September 15 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 13)
    - By City: New York, New York: The New York Society of Security Analysts: 1965 January 12 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 14)
    - By City: New York, New York: Sports Illustrated dinner: 1965 January 25 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 15)
    - By City: New York, New York: The New York Society of Security Analysts: 1966 September 26 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 16)
    - By City: New York, New York: William Caxton Human Relations Award Dinner (Linen as recipient): 1968 December 11 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 17)
    - By City: New York, New York: Pace College Man in Management Award (Linen as recipient): 1969 January 21 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 18)
    - By City: New York, New York: Time Inc. Annual Stockholders Meeting: 1969 April 17 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 19)
    - By City: New York, New York: Time Inc. Address to Management (state of the company): 1969 July 17 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 20)
    - By City: New York, New York: Toastmaster at Pace College Man in Management Dinner: 1970 January 20 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 21)
    - By City: New York, New York: National Urban League Conference: 1970 July 22 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 22)
    - By City: Newark, New Jersey: Council of Social Agencies: 1956 May 9 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 23)
    - By City: Norfolk, Virginia: United Communities Fund: 1962 October 9 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 24)
    - By City: Northampton, Massachusetts: International Student Day at Smith College: 1959 November 18 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 25)
    - By City: Paris, France: ICC [International Chamber of Commerce]: 1967 December 5 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 26)
    - By City: Paris, France: International Chamber of Commerce: 1969 December 3 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 27)
    - By City: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: Health and Welfare Council: 1956 June 21 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 28)
    - By City: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: Poor Richard Club Luncheon: 1958 February 25 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 29)
    - By City: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: United Fund Annual Meeting: 1964 May 28 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 30)
    - By City: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: National Urban League Conference: 1966 August 2 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 31)
    - By City: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: United Fund Report Luncheon: 1956 October 26 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 32)
    - By City: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Health and Welfare Association of Allegheny County: 1959 June 11 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 33)
    - By City: Plainfield, New Jersey: Community Chest Annual Meeting: 1958 February 5 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 34)
    - By City: Phoenix, Arizona: Phoenix Urban League: 1971 April 29 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 35)
    - By City: Port Chester, New York: Royal McBee Management Club: 1960 March 30 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 36)
    - By City: Portland, Oregon: United Fund: 1955 October 4 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 37)
    - By City: Portland, Oregon: Western Conference: 1956 April 11 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 38)
    - By City: Providence, Rhode Island: United Fund Kickoff Dinner: 1956 October 17 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 39a)
    - By City: Rye, New York: Royal McBee Long Range Planning Conference (Westchester County Club): 1958 February 3 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 39b)
    - By City: Saint Louis, Missouri: Community Chests and Councils of America, Inc: Biennial National Conference: 1954 January 28 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 40)
    - By City: Saint Louis, Missouri: Community Welfare Council Leaders Conference: 1957 January 31 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 41)
    - By City: Saint Louis, Missouri: United Community Funds and Councils of America: Biennial: 1960 February 3-4 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 42)
    - By City: Saint Louis, Missouri: Midwestern Area Red Cross National Fund Vice Chairman: 1963 November 17-18 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 43)
    - By City: San Diego, California: Red Cross Kickoff Lunch: 1963 March 1 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 44)
    - By City: San Francisco, California: United Bay Area Crusade Annual Meeting: 1957 January 9 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 45)
    - By City: San Francisco, California: Fibreboard Paper Products Corporation Packaging Group: 1959 December 7 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 46)
    - By City: San Francisco, California: National Paperboard Association Spring Meeting: 1961 May 12 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 47)
    - By City: Sayville, New York: Suffolk Division of Adelphi College Inauguration: 1959 October 28 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 48)
    - By City: Schenectady, New York: Community Chest: 1956 February 16 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 49)
    - By City: Scranton, Pennsylvania: Lackawanna United Fund Kickoff Dinner: 1956 October 8 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 50)
    - By City: Scranton, Pennsylvania: Greater Scranton Chamber of Commerce: 1967 May 6 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 51)
    - By City: Scranton, Pennsylvania: Abington Heights High School Dedication: 1967 November 17 (Offsite-box 4196, Folder 52)
    - By City: Seattle, Washington: United Good Neighbors: 1955 October 6 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 1)
    - By City: Seattle, Washington: Red Cross Convention Fundraising Session: 1962 May 15 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 2)
    - By City: Seattle, Washington: Boeing 50th Anniversary: 1966 July 20 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 3)
    - By City: Shreveport, Louisiana: Community Chest and Countil: 1954 October 13 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 4)
    - By City: Shreveport, Louisiana: Southwest Regional Conference: 1957 April 1 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 5)
    - By City: Simsbury, Connecticut: The Ethel Walker School Commencement Address: 1958 June 8 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 6)
    - By City: Springfield, Massachusetts: United Fund: 1956 January 26 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 7)
    - By City: Stamford, Connecticut: Stamford Community Council Annual Meeting: 1958 June 2 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 8)
    - By City: Syracuse, New York: United Campaign Kickoff: 1962 October 2 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 9)
    - By City: Taipei, Taiwan: Fifth Asian Advertising Congress: 1966 November 7 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 10)
    - By City: Toledo, Ohio: Community Chests and Councils: 1954 September 16 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 11)
    - By City: Toledo, Ohio: Toledo Council of Social Agencies Annual Meeting: 1959 February 19 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 12)
    - By City: Toronto, Ontario, Canada: Community Chests and Councils: 1955 January 29 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 13)
    - By City: Toronto, Ontario, Canada: The Advertising and Sales Club of Toronto: 1959 January 27 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 14)
    - By City: Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada: Community Chest: 1955 October 7 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 15)
    - By City: Waco, Texas: Joint Luncheon Meeting of Civic Clubs for Waco United Fund: 1957 September 18 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 16)
    - By City: Washington, D.C.: United Givers Fund Business Leaders Rally: 1956 September 14 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 17)
    - By City: Washington, D.C.: USO National Council: 1958 March 6 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 18)
    - By City: Washington, D.C.: National Urban League Banquet: 1969 July 30 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 19)
    - By City: Waterbury, [Connecticut]: Community Chests: 1953 February 25 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 20)
    - By City: Wausau, Wisconsin: United Fund Dinner: 1957 September 24 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 21)
    - By City: West Point, New York: southeastern New York Regional Red Cross Conference: 1958 October 14 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 22)
    - By City: Williamstown, Massachusetts: Williams College 25th Reunion: 1959 June 6 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 23)
    - By City: Worchester, Massachusetts: Community Services of Greater Worcester, Inc.-Red Cross: 1962 September 24 (Offsite-box 4197, Folder 24)
  - Subseries II.B.3. Prince of Songkhla University Files, 1965-1970; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    The Prince of Songkla University files contains material regarding Time Inc.'s participation in a project with Thailand and the Overseas Educational Service to establish and support the Prince of Songkla University in southern Thailand. Linen and his assistant John Millington were the primary contacts from Time Inc. and are equally represented in the files. The main correspondents from Thailand are Foreign Minister Thanat Khoman and the first dean of the university Stang Mongkolsuk.
    A good indicator of Time Inc.'s relationship with Thailand during this project is a playful agreement titled the Declaration of the Pacific, which is among Thanat's documents. Its articles declare that receiving chicken at a meal shall be a cause for war, everyone is entitled to eight hours sleep per night, the parties agree to maintain upkeep of golf courses near them, and designates Time Inc.'s and Thailand's enemies so that each may protect the other. Among the enemies listed are Time's main competitor, the editors of Newsweek.
    Organized alphabetically with order imposed.
    - General, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 1-3)
    - Contributor: Eastern Air Lines, Inc., 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 4)
    - Contributor: Union Carbide Corporation, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 5)
    - Education, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 6-7)
    - Educational Advisory Mission to Thailand: 1966 January-February, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 8)
    - Financials, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 9)
    - King of Thailand (Bhumibol Adulyadej): Presentation, 1967 June? (Offsite-box 598, Folder 10-12)
      Includes audiovisual materials.
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container: "Time Inc. Speeches by his Magesty [sic], The King of Thailand. 1. Dinner, 2. Press conference, 3. Williams College." On container: "Speeches by King of Thailand - dinner, Press Conference, Williams College."
      2 audiotape reels: analog, 3.75 ips; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Container label: "Time Inc King of Thailand Presentation. Side 1 Speeches, 2 Entertainment."
    - Millington, John, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 13)
    - Overseas Educational Service: Pamphlets, etc., 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 14)
    - Overseas Educational Service: Bhumibol Adulyadej, King of Thailand: Scholarship Fund, 1968 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 15)
    - Stang Mongkolsuk, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 16)
    - Thailand: General, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 17)
    - Thailand: Research, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 18)
    - Thanat Khoman: General, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 19)
    - Thanat Khoman: Documents, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 20)
    - Thanat Khoman: Documents (Declaration of the Pacific) [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R9)
    - Thanat Khoman: Trips to the United States, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 598, Folder 21)
- Series II.C. Chairman of the Board and Chief Executive Officer: Andrew Heiskell Files, 1949-1980; 9.1 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
  Andrew Heiskell joined Time Inc. in 1937 as an associate editor with Life. Due to his aptitude for and interest in the business side, he was quickly promoted within Life to assistant general manager, general manager, then publisher by 1946. He was appointed a vice president of Time Inc. in 1949 and elected to the board of directors in 1959.
  In 1960, during a major realignment of Time Inc., the board named him chairman at the same time they appointed James Linen as president. During another realignment in 1969, the board designated him the chief executive officer. Heiskell retired from Time Inc. in 1980.
  In 1982, the Magazine Publishers Association named him Publisher of the Year. In 1986, he was inducted into the Publishers Hall of Fame.
  Citation:
  Time Inc. Bio Files, MS 3009-RG 2, New-York Historical Society.
  Andrew Heiskell's files span his time as chairman of the board and chief executive officer of Time Inc. with a small amount of files from prior to his corporate appointment. His files include his correspondence, speeches, and office files organized by subject. His office files include folders with correspondence and documents from other Time Inc. executives and members of the board.
  Organized into three subsubseries:
  Subseries II.C.1. Correspondence
  Subseries II.C.2. Administrative Files
  Subseries II.C.3. Speech Files
  - Subseries II.C.1. Correspondence, 1960-1980; 0.67 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Andrew Heiskell's correspondence is primarily with heads of companies, many of which were advertisers; chairmen of other news organizations such as Katharine Graham of the Washington Post Company; United States senators, including Robert F. Kennedy, regarding policies of interest to Time Inc. such as those involving South America; ambassadors to and from other countries; and some internal correspondence with Time Inc. staff.
    Organized alphabetically by last name based on original order.
    - Correspondence: A-Z, 1960-1980 (Offsite-box 580, Folder 1-24)
  - Subseries II.C.2. Administrative Files, 1958-1980; 7.35 Linear feet in 9 record cartons